Okay, now I can make this video without looking into the camera while I'm reading a script
on the side.
And not just that.
Ahora puedo hablar en español y nunca sabrás que esto es inglés e incluso en Hindi me
bien puedo hablar.
And you will never know whether it's real or fake.
Two AI apps that will make you question reality.
Number one, Captions.ai.
You just have to upload your video to Captions.ai and it will use AI to ensure that you're always
looking into the camera.
It doesn't work if you look at extreme angles or close your eyelids.
How would it look if I put my hand over it?
Is it that good?
Number two, HeyGen.
You can just upload your footage here and then you can choose the language and boom,
done.
To gaitemo, AI no shichio wa mitsuke nikui.
Deepfake mo douyou.
Now HeyGen only lets you do 30 seconds of clip for free but it is so good that paying
for it wouldn't be a bad choice.
However, these two AI sites will make you question reality.